Guide to the Barry Ulanov Papers,
Rare Book and Manuscript Library Columbia University Libraries
- Series II: Writings, 1955-1993
  - Subseries II.2: Writings by Others, 1950s-1990s
    - Sugg, Richard--Jungian Literary Criticism, 1992, (2 Folders) (Box 12, Folder 17 to 18)
    - Trilling, Lionel--"The Arts, etc.," undated (Box 12, Folder 19)
    - Union Suisse des Communautés Israëlites, Documentation Internationale la Persécution des Juifs en Allemagne Attitude des Églises Chrétiennes, undated (Box 16, Folder 4)
    - Zohary, M., Flora of the Bible, 1957 (Box 16, Folder 5)
- Series III: Correspondence, 1940s-2000
  Contained here is correspondence to and from Barry Ulanov between the 1940s and the 2000s. The correspondence within the collection consists primarily of letters regarding Ulanov’s professional activity, particularly as a lecturer and speaker, as well as his work within the Catholic Church. Of particular interest is a handwritten letter to Ulanov from Charles Mingus. The correspondence is arranged chronologically by decade.
  - 1940s (Box 12, Folder 20)
  - 1950s, (2 Folders) (Box 12, Folder 21 to 22)
  - 1960s, (2 Folders) (Box 12, Folder 23 to 24)
  - 1970s (Box 12, Folder 25)
  - 1980s, (2 Folders) (Box 12, Folder 26 to 27)
  - 1990s, (3 Folders) (Box 12, Folder 28 to 30)
  - 1990s, (2 Folders) (Box 13, Folder 1 to 2)
  - 2000 (Box 13, Folder 3)
  - Undated, (2 Folders) (Box 13, Folder 4 to 5)
  - Eucharist Congress, 1964, (2 Folders) (Box 13, Folder 6 to 7)
  - Lecture Records, 1964-1972, (3 Folders) (Box 13, Folder 8 to 10)